classifiedride.com 2016-10-19

# Classified Ride - AUTOMOTIVE CLASSIFIEDS -ClassifiedRide.Com

## Collection of Personal Information

Obviously, information posted to [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) is public information. By providing the site with personal information, you are consenting to [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/)'s collection, use, and disclosure of your information. In addition, you are agreeing to the site transferring and storing your information on our servers. [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) collects the following personal information:

  * Email address, phone numbers, physical contact information
  * Computer sign-on information, stats about page views, and traffic to and from your ad
  * Additional information, including IP address and standard web log information

## With the information collected [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) will

  * Provide the site's services
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot
  * Measure, improve, and/or customize your experience as a site user
  * Provide promotional offers, service updates, and tagged marketing

## Disclosure

[ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) will not sell or rent personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without user consent. However, [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) may disclose personal information in order to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims concerning a posting or violation of other's rights, or to protect user rights, property, or safety. Also, [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) may share information with: corporate affiliates to prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services, service providers who assist with our business operations, third-party websites and publishers so your ads can reach a broader clientele.

## Registration and sharing

[ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) may offer single sign-on services that allow you to use third party login credentials to sign in to the site. With permission, [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) may also transfer profile information from said third party sites.

## Communication

Marketing communications will be sent from [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) via email unless you tell you wish otherwise. You may NOT harvest addresses, send spam or otherwise breach our Terms of Agreement or Privacy Policy via our website. Additionally, [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/) reserves the right to automatically or manually scan and/or filter email messages sent via our site for malicious activity or prohibited content. These messages, however, will not be permanently stored by [ClassifiedRide.com](http://classifiedride.com/).
